Guide to the Hermann Broch Archive
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Addition, 1925-1990s; Series VI; 3.83
  - Writings
    - "Psychische Selbstbiographie" and "Nachtrag zu meiner Psychischen Selbstbiographie," typescript carbon and English translation, typescript, with related correspondence (Box 76)
    - Die Schlafwandler, page proof, corrected (Box 76)
    - Die Schuldlosen, page proof, corrected (Box 76)
    - Tagebuch in Briefen an Ea von Allesch, papers concerning translation (Box 76)
    - Other writings, printed (Box 76)
  - Writings of others
    - Writing About Broch
      - Kahler, Alice Loewy, poems and notes (Box 76)
      - Kahler, Erich, poem (Box 76)
      - Other authors (Box 76–77)
    - General
      - Unidentified (Box 77)
  - Personal Papers
    - Autograph album, 1925-1926 (Box 78)
    - Death certificate, photocopy (Box 78)
    - Clippings, photocopies, and ephemera, 3 (Box 78)
  - Photographs
    - Hermann Broch
      - Photographs of Hermann Broch, member of the Broch family, and others (Box 78)
    - Other
      - Unidentified (Box 78)
- Restricted Material
  Restricted during the lifetime of Sachiko Yoshizawa Broch
  - Restricted material (Box 80)
    Restricted during the life of Sachiko Yoshizawa Broch de Rothermann. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
- Oversize, 1907-87; 2; (2 boxes) + 2 art storage items, 1 roll
  Oversize (Boxes 73-74, 79 roll) is composed of materials from Series II, III, IV, and VI. The papers are arranged in an order consistent with that of the original series.
  - WRITINGS
    - Books
      - Bergroman
        - The Spell: dust jackets, 1987 (Box 73 (Oversize), Folder 1796)
      - Die Schlafwandler
        - Book reviews, 1951-83, n.d. (Box 73 (Oversize), Folder 1797)
        - Scrapbook, n.d. (Box 73 (Oversize), Folder 1798)
      - Die Schuldlosen: galley proofs, corrected, with printer's annotations, n.d. (Box 73 (Oversize), Folder 1799)
      - Der Tod des Vergil: book reviews, 1945-63 (Box 73 (Oversize), Folder 1800)
    - Plays
      - Die Entsühnung: posters, 1979, n.d. (Box 74 (Oversize), Folder 1801)
    - Shorter Works: Articles and Essays
      - "Geist und Zeitgeist": poster (Box 74 (Oversize), Folder 1802)
  - WRITINGS OF OTHERS
    - General
      - Federn, Paul, "Die Vier Frongesetze der Zwangsneurose,": galley proofs, corrected, n.d. (Box 74 (Oversize), Folder 1803)
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - Clippings, 1946 (Box 74 (Oversize), Folder 1804)
    - Death mask: list of subscribers, ca. 1951 (Box 74 (Oversize), Folder 1805)
    - Patents for cotton textile machinery, 1907 (Box 74 (Oversize), Folder 1806)
    - von Ripper, Rudolph: drawing of Hermann Broch, n.d. (Box 74a (Oversize), Folder 1806a)
  - ITEMS IN ART STORAGE
    - Rothstein bust (Box Art, Folder 1806b)
    - Death mask (Box Art, Folder 1806c)
  - ADDITION
    - Die Erzählung der Magd Zerline, posters (Box 79 Roll)